{
    "subject": "Judith_of_Habsburg",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Wenceslaus_II_of_Bohemia",
    "human_readable": "Judith of Habsburg is married to Wenceslaus II of Bohemia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9887086749076843,
            "question": "Is Wenceslaus II of Bohemia married to Judith of Habsburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9404206871986389,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Judith of Habsburg and Wenceslaus II of Bohemia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9386069178581238,
            "question": "Name the wife of Wenceslaus II of Bohemia."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9224404692649841,
            "question": "Who is Judith of Habsburg married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9133040308952332,
            "question": "Who is associated with the marriage to Wenceslaus II of Bohemia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8597369194030762,
            "question": "Who was the husband of Judith of Habsburg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8347563743591309,
            "question": "To whom was Judith of Habsburg wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7428587675094604,
            "question": "What is the name of Judith of Habsburg's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7353857755661011,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Judith of Habsburg's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5830695033073425,
            "question": "What is Judith of Habsburg known for?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Judith of Habsburg is married to Wenceslaus II of Bohemia.",
            "html": "yago_31225_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me about Judith of Habsburg's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_31225_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Judith of Habsburg's husband?",
            "html": "yago_31225_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To whom was Judith of Habsburg wed?",
            "html": "yago_31225_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_31225_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "**Rewrite**\n\nJudith of Habsburg is married to Wenceslaus II of Bohemia. \n\nContext: The document at file_path `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_31225/re-ranker-msmarco/41.txt` confirms this union, specifying that Judith was the daughter of Holy Roman Emperor Rudolf I."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " Yes"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}